[{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664133883,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":17585,"timeElapsed":149185},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664147328,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":13443,"timeElapsed":162630},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664169458,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":22127,"timeElapsed":184760},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664174564,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":5104,"timeElapsed":189866},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664181050,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":6484,"timeElapsed":196352},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664184136,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3084,"timeElapsed":199438},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664187215,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3077,"timeElapsed":202517},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664194808,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":7592,"timeElapsed":210110},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664200258,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":5448,"timeElapsed":215560},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664212603,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":11102,"timeElapsed":227904},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664215734,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3131,"timeElapsed":231036},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664220054,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4317,"timeElapsed":235356},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664222950,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2894,"timeElapsed":238252},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664227120,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":4169,"timeElapsed":242422},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664230710,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":3588,"timeElapsed":246012},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664236890,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":6179,"timeElapsed":252192},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664262076,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":25184,"timeElapsed":277378},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664265162,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3085,"timeElapsed":280464},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664274200,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":7819,"timeElapsed":289502},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664276588,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2387,"timeElapsed":291890},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664281442,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":4853,"timeElapsed":296744},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664283994,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2551,"timeElapsed":299296},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664286632,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2637,"timeElapsed":301934},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664289404,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2770,"timeElapsed":304706},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664292160,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2754,"timeElapsed":307462},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664294908,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2747,"timeElapsed":310210},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664297490,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"43","question":"What is your least favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2580,"timeElapsed":312792},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664312518,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":14107,"timeElapsed":327820},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664314818,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2299,"timeElapsed":330120},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664317832,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":3013,"timeElapsed":333134},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664320572,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2739,"timeElapsed":335874},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664323054,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":2481,"timeElapsed":338356},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664326461,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3406,"timeElapsed":341762},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664329954,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":3492,"timeElapsed":345256},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664339518,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":9563,"timeElapsed":354820},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664349812,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":10293,"timeElapsed":365114},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664369794,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":18843,"timeElapsed":385096},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664376192,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":6397,"timeElapsed":391494},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664379028,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2835,"timeElapsed":394330},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664385026,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":5997,"timeElapsed":400328},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664388960,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":3933,"timeElapsed":404262},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664390876,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1915,"timeElapsed":406178},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664393206,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":2329,"timeElapsed":408508},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664396990,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":3783,"timeElapsed":412291},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664404252,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7261,"timeElapsed":419554},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664409772,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":5519,"timeElapsed":425074},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664417750,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":6955,"timeElapsed":433052},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664420074,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":2323,"timeElapsed":435376},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664423346,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":3271,"timeElapsed":438648},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664426032,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2685,"timeElapsed":441334},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664431619,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":5586,"timeElapsed":446921},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664435216,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3595,"timeElapsed":450518},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664456098,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":20881,"timeElapsed":471400},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664459128,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":3028,"timeElapsed":474430},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664465621,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":6492,"timeElapsed":480923},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664467906,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":2283,"timeElapsed":483207},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664478056,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":9175,"timeElapsed":493358},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664480538,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2481,"timeElapsed":495839},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664483410,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2871,"timeElapsed":498712},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664487728,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":4317,"timeElapsed":503030},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664490272,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2543,"timeElapsed":505574},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664492515,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2242,"timeElapsed":507817},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664495342,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":2825,"timeElapsed":510644},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664498600,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3257,"timeElapsed":513902},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664505140,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"75","question":"If you opened a restaurant, what would it be like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":6539,"timeElapsed":520442},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664558030,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":51954,"timeElapsed":573331},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664560635,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2605,"timeElapsed":575937},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664583559,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":22923,"timeElapsed":598861},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664612105,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":28545,"timeElapsed":627407},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664616477,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":4370,"timeElapsed":631779},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664620356,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3878,"timeElapsed":635658},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664625434,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":5077,"timeElapsed":640736},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664629507,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4072,"timeElapsed":644809},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664632349,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2841,"timeElapsed":647651},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664673057,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":39734,"timeElapsed":688359},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664675083,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":2025,"timeElapsed":690385},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664677673,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":2589,"timeElapsed":692975},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664680851,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":3177,"timeElapsed":696153},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664684533,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":3681,"timeElapsed":699835},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664687013,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2479,"timeElapsed":702315},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664690639,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3625,"timeElapsed":705941},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664693919,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":3279,"timeElapsed":709221},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664697177,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":3257,"timeElapsed":712479},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664704343,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":6098,"timeElapsed":719645},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664709475,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":5131,"timeElapsed":724777},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664715157,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":5681,"timeElapsed":730459},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664718415,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3257,"timeElapsed":733717},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664738337,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":19921,"timeElapsed":753639},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664741209,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2871,"timeElapsed":756511},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664744191,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2981,"timeElapsed":759493},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664746609,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2417,"timeElapsed":761911},{"subjectID":"y6zuewhn75","prolificID":"63e63f77c742a91baf498dd0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421664b8a77abed200a5b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664749575,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2965,"timeElapsed":764877}]